upsto.re 2019-05-01

# Privacy policy — Upload, store & share your files on Upstore

## Privacy policy

Please read this entire notice. **_up_ sto.re** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the **_up_ sto.re** Web site.

By using the Site, you signify your assent to our privacy policy. If you do not agree with any of the terms of this policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy when they go into effect.

**I. Information That We Collect and What We Do With the Collected Information, Including Disclosures to Third Parties.**

There are situations when using our Web site when we may need personal information from you. By "personal information" we mean information that is uniquely identified to you, such as your name, email address, IP address, password and user name.

We may disclose in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties, such as advertisers or potential advertisers. Those disclosures do not include personal information.

**_up_ sto.re** might use information collected in connection with your participation in interactive activities, including account registration, for its own internal purposes, such as (by way of illustration) to respond to inquiries, to enforce the Terms of Use, or to defend itself in the event of litigation. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We also can use the IP address to verify the identity of perpetrators of illegal activity. 

**2\. Other Disclosures to Third Parties - subpoenas, court and government orders, our attorneys.**

**_up_ sto.re** will not distribute or sell any of your personal information to third parties. 

However, by using this site's services, you assume the risk that a court or government agency may order **_up_ sto.re** to disclose your submission and/or personally identifying information about you, or that a litigant, a court, a grand jury, or government agency may subpoena that information.

We do not disclose the identities of ours users unless we are legally required to do so. If a governmental agency (for example, law enforcement agencies, US Attorneys' offices or similar governmental agencies) sends us a subpoena, we will comply with it.

We will attempt to notify you of such a subpoena or other legal process by sending a notice by electronic mail to the most recent e-mail address you have provided to us. The notice will include basic information concerning the subpoena, court order, or legal process (i.e., name of lawsuit, case number, place of filing, party issuing subpoena, the court where the subpoena was issued, contact information, deadline by which we plan to comply with the process, etc.). 

**_up_ sto.re** may need to consult its own attorneys. In doing so, **_up_ sto.re** may disclose personal information to its attorneys. 

We cannot advise you regarding the law or an appropriate response to a subpoena. Should you wish to oppose a subpoena or other legal process, you should seek legal advice concerning applicable rights and procedures that might be available. 

**3\. Security**

The **_up_ sto.re** Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We back up the data on a daily basis, and have password protected access levels which insure legitimate site administration. 

The **_up_ sto.re** Web site contains links to other Web sites. **_up_ sto.re** is not responsible for the security practices of the Web sites that are linked from our site. We highly recommend that visitors check the privacy statements at these linked sites. 

**4\. Cookies**

There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some **_up_ sto.re** pages use cookies so that we can better serve you when you visit and then return to our site. We use cookies to deliver information specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit certain areas of our Web site. 

**5\. Modify Your Information**

The **_up_ sto.re** site provides users with the opportunity to change or modify information previously provided. If you would like to change or modify your information, please visit your 'My Account' page.

**Additional Information**   
Any questions relating to our Privacy Policies may be directed to **_up_ sto.re** using the contact form.  

**April 1, 2012**
